<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cork Travel App</string>
    <string name="welcomeMessage">Welcome to Cork Travel App! What are you looking for?</string>
    <string name="shelbourneBar">One of The Shelbourne\'\s treasures - The Horseshoe Bar has always been a destination, an institution and a living history of Irish society. From business and politics to the arts, it has been home to some of Ireland\'\s most fascinating characters since 1957. A warm and intimate bar for a perfect pint of plain, a beloved local whiskey or a well-built martini. The curved brass-trimmed bar and rich red walls create an atmospheric setting where the customer is only a few feet from the bartender and the next round.</string>
    <string name="costigansPub">Costigan’s Traditional Irish pub is without doubt one of Cork’s oldest and finest pubs, nestled in the heart of Washington Street, Cork City. What began as a Fish Mongers, then became a coach house and years later a sweet shop, it blossomed into the charming pub that it is today. Through the centuries it has retained its Irish character. It is an old style public house with its long bar counter, snug and parlour area; not to mention the open fire and heated beer garden. We are very proud of our extensive Irish whiskey.</string>
    <string name="corkArms">The Cork Arms is a hidden gem, in a busy world. It has been a family run business for generations, and the current owners are Patsy and Laurence O’ Leary. It is located at 23 McCurtain St, one of Cork’s busiest streets, home to numerous pubs and restaurants, and part of Cork’s burgeoning Victorian Quarter.</string>
    <string name="oliverPlunkett">CRAIC &amp; CEOL, At The Oliver Plunkett, live music and entertainment are at the forefront of our business. We currently have a wide variety of live music every Wednesday through Sunday. Please see our social media pages for our Monthly music schedule.</string>
    <string name="theCornerHouse">Here we have a truly traditional Irish Pub In the heart of Cork City. This family run pub since 1994 has hosted many talented musicians and artists. It is the original home of the Murphys Folk Club, Cork, and is currently the home of Lee Delta Blues Club. Come and enjoy a cozy atmosphere, friendly chat and the finest Irish stout and porter. Drop in, listen to the tunes, and have a pint.</string>
    <string name="elbowLane">SET IN A HANDSOME BUILDING AT THE END OF OLIVER PLUNKETT STREET IN CORK CITY, OUR RESTAURANT COMBINES AN IN-HOUSE NANO BREWERY WITH A SMOKE HOUSE SERVING EXCITING FOOD AND DRINKS INCLUDING OUR OWN ELBOW LANE BEERS.</string>
    <string name="riverClub">The River Club brings an exciting new dimension to Corks thriving restaurant and bar scene. With a cool New York vibe in the bar, sophisticated dining in the Grill Room and a distinctly relaxed Mediterranean feel on the riverside terrace, The River Club, is Corks ultimate destination to eat, drink and be social.</string>
    <string name="libertyGrill">Our New England influenced all-day brunch menu features classics like Eggs Benedict and French Toast, and our lunch and dinner menus include a choice of burgers, salads and steaks. All our menus feature a selection of dishes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, along with a range of seafood and fish dishes sourced from the nearby Cork English Market. Join us soon at Liberty Grill for a hearty (or healthy) breakfast, a catch-up over morning coffee, a celebration with family and friends, dress down business or that special dinner date.</string>
</resources>